goldencan.com 2017-11-29

# GoldenCAN Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

GoldenCAN™ is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy and Security Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. 

The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information GoldenCAN.com may gather about individuals who visit its Web site, how that information is used, and GoldenCAN.com's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to GoldenCAN.com's Web site only, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links. 

**Site Usage Information**

GoldenCAN.com gathers "site usage" information from all visitors to the GoldenCAN.com Web site. Such data is used in the aggregate, to help determine general usage patterns and fine tune layout in order to ensure that our site is as useful and enjoyable as possible. This "site usage" and statistical information may be made public information at GoldenCAN.com's discretion. Additionally, at the sole discretion of any merchant or affiliate program manager, basic information may be disclosed in compliance with the Terms and Conditions of third party affiliate programs or corresponding merchants. We will earnestly provide the least sensitive information needed to assist any inquiries from any parties involved. 

**Third Party Information**

GoldenCAN.com may also gather personal information regarding protocol for third party companies' procedures. This is done to ensure proper activity within known third party terms and conditions. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. You may later access and modify the information provided, or have it removed. 

**Use of Cookies**

When you view our Web site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a 'Cookie' and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor our Web site to better match your interests and preferences and optionally provide automatic member login. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

**Individual User Information**

GoldenCAN.com will collect personal information if you choose to become a GoldenCAN.com member. The personal information we collect includes your name, e-mail, and/or work phone, work or home address, company or organization name. We do not share either e-mail addresses or individually identifiable information with any third parties. 

**Disclosure**

GoldenCAN.com reserves the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its users. Where practical, GoldenCAN.com will attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual prior to disclosing individually identifiable information. As mentioned above, we reserve the right to share aggregated "site usage" information with third parties. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or believe that we have not adhered to the guidelines set forth above, please contact us. 

Thank you 

GoldenCAN Staff
